// St Patricks day multi questions
// CS --> Added One, Two and Three to the questions to make sure that if we change the round it is retrieving the correct array
const roundOneQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Who is St. Patrick?",
        options: ["The Irish Prime-Minister", "The most famous Irish patron saint", "The most famous priest in Ireland"],
        answer: "The most famous Irish patron saint"
    },
    {
        question: "What did St. Patrick got Ireland rid of?",
        options: ["Cows", "Dogs", "Snakes"],
        answer: "Snakes"
    },
    {
        question: "What is celebrated on March 17?",
        options: ["St. Patrick's Day", "Easter", "Christmas"],
        answer: "St. Patrick's Day"
    },
    {
        question: "When was St. Patrick's day celebrated for the first time?",
        options: ["1902", "1903", "1904"],
        answer: "1903"
    },
    {
        question: "What is St. Patrick's nationality?",
        options: ["British", "Dutch", "Irish"],
        answer: "British"
    },
    {
        question: "What is St. Patrick's real name",
        options: ["Conor", "Maewyn", "Finn"],
        answer: "Maewyn"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the color used on St. Patrick's day?",
        options: ["Green", "Blue", "Orange"],
        answer: "Green"
    },
    {
        question: "To which religion were the Irish converted by St. Patrick?",
        options: ["Islamism", "Christianism", "Paganism"],
        answer: "Christianism"
    },
    {
        question: "What is a St. Patrick's classic dish?",
        options: ["Corned beef and Cabbage", "Irish Seafood Chowder", "Colcannon"],
        answer: "Corned beef and Cabbage"
    },
    {
        question: "How was St. Patrick brought to Ireland?",
        options: ["As a farmer", "As a priest", "As a slave"],
        answer: "As a slave"
    },
];

const roundTwoQuestions = [
    {
        question: "St. Patrick is Irish.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "Beer is the most drank beverage on St. Patrick's day",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        question: "St. Patrick preferred blue over green.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        question: "St. Patrick used a shamrock to explain the Holy Trinity.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        question: "Corned beef and cabbage is St. Patrick's classic dish",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        question: "St. Patrick got rid of all the cows on Ireland",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "St. Patrick's day is also referred as St. Paddy's day",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        question: "Maewyn is St. Patrick's real name",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        question: "St. Patrick is not a patron saint of Ireland",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "Pubs have always been allowed to open on St. Patrick's day",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
];

const roundThreeQuestions = [
    {
        question: "What is the biggest lake of Ireland?",
        options: ["Lough Derg", "Lough Neagh", "Lough Corrib"],
        answer: "Lough Neagh"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these counties has the biggest population?",
        options: ["Cork", "Limerick", "Galway"],
        answer: "Cork"
    },
    {
        question: "Which county is nicknamed The Treaty County?",
        options: ["Carlow", "Waterford", "Limerick"],
        answer: "Limerick"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the longest river on Ireland?",
        options: ["River Shannon", "Grand Canal", "River Barrow"],
        answer: "River Shannon"
    },
    {
        question: "In terms of match attendance, what is the most popular sport in Ireland?",
        options: ["American Football", "Gaelic Football", "Soccer"],
        answer: "Gaelic Football"
    },
    {
        question: "In what language is the Book of Kells written?",
        options: ["English", "Gaelic", "Latin"],
        answer: "Latin"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Ireland's capital?",
        options: ["Lucan", "Dublin", "Cork"],
        answer: "Dublin"
    },
    {
        question: "Being drunk in public is an offence",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        question: "More Irish live inside of Ireland than out",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        question: "Gay marriage is legal in Ireland",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
];